dishant.com 2016-03-10

# Sangeethouse.com - Home of Indian Music - Privacy Policy

**Privacy Statement for Sangeethouse.Com**

Sangeethouse.com has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site: Sangeethouse.com

**Information Automatically Logged**

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our Web site. Your IP address is also used to gather broad demographic information for the purpose of constantly improving the contents of our Web site to suit the needs of our visitors. We do not use your IP address for any other purposes.

**Third Party Advertising**

We use MaxWorldwide and other third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web  
site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please click here [ http://www.maxonline.com/privacy_policy/index.php](http://www.maxonline.com/privacy_policy/index.php)

Third Party Cookies In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique "cookie" on your browser.

**Personal Information**

The personal information you provide to us viz. name, email address, etc. allows us to inform you about updates to the service and to notify you of products and services of Sangeethouse.com. We also share aggregate of these information, not individual data, with our advertisers to help them better understand our services and to monitor the reach of their advertising on the service.

We do not share, sell or use any of the identifiable personal information to any third parties under any circumstances unless we are required to do so by law.

**Security**

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control.

**Contacting the Web Site**

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact us using this link
